<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coleman Rollins&#39; Portfolio</title>
    <description>Portfolio site for Coleman Rollins, Web Developer
</description>
    <link>http://colemanrollins.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://colemanrollins.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 17:06:28 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 17:06:28 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minneapolis Is Beautiful</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is a beautiful day in Minneapolis. I’ve set up on the bank of lake Calhoun with my bike and my computer to sit and work, and to soak in what is arguably the best time of the year in this city. I’ve spent so much time and effort thinking/worrying/stressing about how I’m going to get TF out of here, that I sometimes forget how great Minneapolis actually is. Don’t get me wrong, I’m still going to move, but I will always have the utmost appreciation for my hometown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s crazy even thinking about living somewhere else. Crazy and scary, which is why I need to do it. I feel like I’ve hit a plateau that I can’t escape. A plateau in my personal, professional and emotional development that can only be cured by forcing myself out of my comfort zone. I love my friends and my family, but I just can’t get over the feeling that I need a change. It’s really fucking stressful, and every day that goes by where I’m not working towards my goal just stresses me out even more. My Mom and I have talked a lot about this; sometimes we put too much pressure on ourselves, which can be unhealthy. At the same time, it’s hard not to put pressure on myself when I know I have goals out there that I need to reach. Ugh. It’s just one big thing on my mind at all times. Mix in a less-than-ideal work situation with some unhealthy lingering ties in the city and I’m pretty much going insane.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, I’m doing my best to make it happen, and I have some awesome friends and family helping me along the way. Also I just set up a brand new A/C unit in my apartment, so hopefully I wont be going insane AND melting. Next blog post will be about my brand new Pebble Time :), maybe even some pictures and an unboxing video will be in order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coleman&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://colemanrollins.io/2015/06/07/some-things.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://colemanrollins.io/2015/06/07/some-things.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jekyll FTW</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Whoooo hooooo! To anyone reading this, you’re seeing the fruits of my most recent weekend project. I’ve completely rebuilt my site using an awesome static site generator tool called Jekyll. It probably doesn’t look very different from the outside, but it’s all new! This site is hosted on GitHub-Pages, which means there isn’t any possibility for server-side template/CMS tools such as Flask, which I had originally planned on using. Since I don’t want to pay for hosting and move all my stuff, I had to check out Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the inception of my portfolio site I had written it ALL by hand, which included a ton of boilerplate HTML. I didn’t know any other way to successfully host my site on gh-pages. Obviously this wasn’t ideal, and made it a pain in the ass to update or modify in any way. Thankfully, there was Jekyll. Jekyll uses the Liquid templating system to give you the freedom to create layouts/variables for different types of content and simply add each piece using markdown. Not to mention you can “include” chunks of HTML incredibly easily, which eliminated the need to update the head/header on EVERY page if one stylesheet or js file needed to be added. Jekyll is built with Ruby and simply spits out your site as static files using the command line. Highly recommend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ALSO. Now that I can add content this easily, I’ve decided to start a blog section for my site. I’m not really sure what kinds of things I’m going to post about, but it will include cool new coding things I’m trying out, tech reviews (I’m getting the Pebble Time soon :) ) and random feels. Keep an eye out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coleman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://colemanrollins.io/2015/05/24/jekyll-ftw.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://colemanrollins.io/2015/05/24/jekyll-ftw.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
