<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coleman Rollins&#39; Portfolio</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://colemanrollins.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://colemanrollins.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 12:55:01 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2015 12:55:01 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jekyll FTW</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Whoooo hooooo! To anyone reading this, you’re seeing the fruits of my most recent weekend project. I’ve completely rebuilt my site using an awesome static site generator tool called Jekyll. It probably doesn’t look very different from the outside, but it’s all new! This site is hosted on GitHub-Pages, which means there isn’t any possibility for server-side template/CMS tools such as Flask, which I had originally planned on using. Since I don’t want to pay for hosting and move all my stuff, I had to check out Jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the inception of my portfolio site I had written it ALL by hand, which included a ton of boilerplate HTML. I didn’t know any other way to successfully host my site on gh-pages. Obviously this wasn’t ideal, and made it a pain in the ass to update or modify in any way. Thankfully, there was Jekyll. Jekyll uses the Liquid templating system to give you the freedom to create layouts/variables for different types of content and simply add each piece using markdown. Not to mention you can “include” chunks of HTML incredibly easily, which eliminated the need to update the head/header on EVERY page if one stylesheet or js file needed to be added. Jekyll is built with Ruby and simply spits out your site as static files using the command line. Highly recommend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ALSO. Now that I can add content this easily, I’ve decided to start a blog section for my site. I’m not really sure what kinds of things I’m going to post about, but it will include cool new coding things I’m trying out, tech reviews (I’m getting the Pebble Time soon :) ) and random feels. Keep an eye out!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coleman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://colemanrollins.io/2015/05/24/jekyll-ftw.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://colemanrollins.io/2015/05/24/jekyll-ftw.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
